<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-11T22:10:46-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Maggie Delano</title><subtitle>Maggie Delano is an Assistant Professor at Swarthmore College working on medical devices for patients with chronic diseases. She's also interested in inclusive engineering design.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Transitioning to Professor Life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/transitioning-to-professor-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Transitioning to Professor Life" /><published>2019-01-08T19:17:49-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-08T19:17:49-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/transitioning-to-professor-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/transitioning-to-professor-life.html">&lt;p&gt;Four and a half years ago I wrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://maggiedelano.tumblr.com/2020/07/11/2014-06-10-doing-whats-important.html&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; about my priorities and doing what was important to me at the time as a graduate student in the middle of her PhD. Fast forward to today, and I defended my PhD (over a year ago!) and have started a tenure track assistant professor position at Swarthmore College (hurray!). The last year has been a total whirlwind; I moved in early January 2018, turned in my thesis a few weeks later, and then started teaching about 4 days after that. I’ve been getting used to a new job, a new city, and just closed on a condo in December. It’s like jamming a whole ton of adulting all into one year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the dust is starting to settle a bit, I’m realizing that I don’t entirely know what I actually want to prioritize for the coming years (especially outside of work). All my energy had been focused on getting &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; the faculty position, and the last year I’ve been adjusting, but now I’m here and need to decide what I want the next stage of my life to look like holistically. On the one hand, I feel like I have so many options and possibilities; on the other, I feel like need to stay focused for the long haul to make a dent in the meaningful ways I aspire to. All the things that were on my “someday after grad school” list are now begging for attention and it’s overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A major change about moving from grad school to a faculty position is the myriad of different tasks and roles one needs to juggle. For me, this includes research, teaching, service, and professional development. Then within each of those categories are different projects, courses, students to advise, recommendation letters to write, committees to sit on, etc. I finally caved and purchased an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omnigroup.com/&quot;&gt;OmniFocus 3&lt;/a&gt; license in a moment of overwhelm just to keep all the things in one place in a coherent manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One disappointing thing about the move and job transition was that it didn’t solve all my problems (shocking, I know). Many things that I thought would be improved by a change of pace and environment really did improve, but not everything. I still have a lot to work on and need to take the time to figure out who I want to be and what I want to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After mulling things over, I decided the best thing to do is come back to my previous posts and evaluate a new set of goals and priorities. My main categories from last time were  &lt;strong&gt;self-improvement&lt;/strong&gt; , &lt;strong&gt;meaningful work&lt;/strong&gt; , and &lt;strong&gt;quality time with friends and family&lt;/strong&gt;. I think I still value meaningful work and quality time with friends and family, but I want to re-frame “self-improvement” to “self-care.” Perfectionism is a big challenge for me, and I think that thinking about taking care of myself rather than trying to make myself “better” will contribute more positively to my well-being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within those categories, here’s some of my priorities and how they are going:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self-care&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to self-care, I’ll divide this into mental health, physical health, and finances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mental health:&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve been working on trying to be nice to myself, instead of always pushing myself to be “better.” I do still want to do my best, but I’m trying to recognize the ways in pushing myself can be counterproductive. I’m also trying to think about things to do that help me recharge, and letting myself do things just for fun. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Physical health:&lt;/strong&gt; I walk a lot for work, but I haven’t otherwise picked up a regular exercise habit in several years, so I want to get back to that. I’ve been reasonably good at cooking for myself and want to keep that up and start bringing my lunches more often.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finances:&lt;/strong&gt; I bought a condo! I also budget regularly and try to save money, which I’m mostly happy with. Once the dust settles, I want to re-evaluate how much I’m saving each month and make sure I’m saving a percentage of my income in line with my long term goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meaningful Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost all of my work right now is focused on my faculty job, which divides itself into a few categories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research:&lt;/strong&gt; I’m currently wrapping up all the papers, presentations, etc. that are primarily based on my PhD work and transitioning into all new work. I’m happy with my current project and direction (a continuation of my heart failure monitoring project from grad school).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching:&lt;/strong&gt; I really enjoy teaching and it was a major reason to go into academia. I’ve been developing courses including embedded systems, and computer architecture, and next spring I’ll be teaching my first inclusive design course.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service:&lt;/strong&gt; Swarthmore gives new faculty one year of service relief, but starting this upcoming semester I’ll be on our Maker Space committee. I also have a bunch of freshmen advisees I’ve been working with. I’m looking forward to learning more about the experiences of students using the Maker Space and our new students and supporting them.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development and Learning New Things:&lt;/strong&gt; I’m learning so much in the areas already mentioned above, but I do want to prioritize learning new skills for fun or related to work in the new year if I have enough down time. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quality time with friends and family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving to a new city has been a big change socially. I’ve been trying to find the balance between making and deepening new connections with staying in touch with family and friends in other cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Making new connections:&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve met tons of great colleagues already, and look forward to working and hanging out with them in the coming years. I’ve made fewer connections outside of Swarthmore, but I like the people I have gotten to know and I’m working on getting to know more people here and there. I’m hoping in the new year I’ll have more time to have a hobby or at least have people over at my new place.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Staying in touch:&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve never been particularly good at staying in touch with people I don’t see on a regular basis. I’m trying to stay in more regular contact with at least a few people, and because I travel back to Boston often maintaining some of those friendships has been a little easier. I’ve been working to identify the relationships that I value most and the frequency at which I’d like to be in contact with those people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past year has been a lot of personal development and growing all at once, but I think I’m coming out of it stronger. My goal for before the semester begins is to come up with more concrete goals and thoughts on how to balance all the different areas of focus I have (while maintaining my sanity and having a little fun too).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="reflections" /><summary type="html">Four and a half years ago I wrote this post about my priorities and doing what was important to me at the time as a graduate student in the middle of her PhD. Fast forward to today, and I defended my PhD (over a year ago!) and have started a tenure track assistant professor position at Swarthmore College (hurray!). The last year has been a total whirlwind; I moved in early January 2018, turned in my thesis a few weeks later, and then started teaching about 4 days after that. I’ve been getting used to a new job, a new city, and just closed on a condo in December. It’s like jamming a whole ton of adulting all into one year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Inclusive Language in Research Articles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/11/16/using-inclusive-language-in-research-articles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Inclusive Language in Research Articles" /><published>2015-11-16T22:31:31-05:00</published><updated>2015-11-16T22:31:31-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/11/16/using-inclusive-language-in-research-articles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/11/16/using-inclusive-language-in-research-articles.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@maggied/using-inclusive-language-in-research-articles-3790b1def91c&quot;&gt;Using Inclusive Language in Research Articles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In which I rewrite a paragraph from a research article that uses uninclusive language.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="phd" /><category term="feminism" /><category term="gender" /><category term="research" /><category term="language" /><category term="inclusion" /><summary type="html">Using Inclusive Language in Research Articles</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My first podcast appearance!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/10/30/my-first-podcast-appearance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first podcast appearance!" /><published>2015-10-30T15:26:18-04:00</published><updated>2015-10-30T15:26:18-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/10/30/my-first-podcast-appearance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/10/30/my-first-podcast-appearance.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://justtalkingpodcast.com/2015/08/11/with-maggie-delano/&quot;&gt;My first podcast appearance!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was interviewed for my first podcast ever! Listen to me talk about Quantified Self, my research, periods and more on the Just Talking podcast.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="quantified self" /><category term="periods" /><category term="period tracking" /><category term="podcasts" /><category term="phd" /><category term="habits" /><summary type="html">My first podcast appearance!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maggie Delano: Building Myself Back Up</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/10/28/maggie-delano-building-myself-back-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maggie Delano: Building Myself Back Up" /><published>2015-10-28T19:50:09-04:00</published><updated>2015-10-28T19:50:09-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/10/28/maggie-delano-building-myself-back-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/10/28/maggie-delano-building-myself-back-up.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantifiedself.com/2015/08/maggie-delano-building-back/&quot;&gt;Maggie Delano: Building Myself Back Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gave this presentation at the 2015 Quantified Self Global Conference. In the talk, I discuss how I built myself back up after my &lt;a href=&quot;http://maggiedelano.tumblr.com/2020/07/11/2014-10-19-browsing-without-hurting-my-brain.html&quot;&gt;concussion&lt;/a&gt; using tools such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sleepio.com/&quot;&gt;Sleepio&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://habitica.com&quot;&gt;Habitrpg&lt;/a&gt; (now Habitica). Check out the video for more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sleepio" /><category term="habitica" /><category term="habitrpg" /><category term="quantified self" /><category term="habits" /><summary type="html">Maggie Delano: Building Myself Back Up</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I tried tracking my period and it was even worse than I could have imagined</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/03/22/i-tried-tracking-my-period-and-it-was-even-worse.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I tried tracking my period and it was even worse than I could have imagined" /><published>2015-03-22T17:15:23-04:00</published><updated>2015-03-22T17:15:23-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/03/22/i-tried-tracking-my-period-and-it-was-even-worse</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/03/22/i-tried-tracking-my-period-and-it-was-even-worse.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@maggied/i-tried-tracking-my-period-and-it-was-even-worse-than-i-could-have-imagined-bb46f869f45&quot;&gt;I tried tracking my period and it was even worse than I could have imagined&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;While people track periods for a whole variety of reasons, self-tracking apps would have you think otherwise. This is a cross-post of my original medium post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="period" /><category term="period tracking" /><category term="quantified self" /><category term="self-tracking" /><category term="apps" /><summary type="html">I tried tracking my period and it was even worse than I could have imagined</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Browsing without hurting my brain</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/10/19/browsing-without-hurting-my-brain.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Browsing without hurting my brain" /><published>2014-10-19T20:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2014-10-19T20:34:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/10/19/browsing-without-hurting-my-brain</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/10/19/browsing-without-hurting-my-brain.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been recovering from &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Post-concussion_syndrome&quot;&gt;Post-Concussion Syndrome&lt;/a&gt; for the past 7 weeks or so. Now that I’ve been getting back to work, I wanted to share a few things that I’ve found particularly helpful for keeping up with my work without hurting my brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first things I’ve learned to do better are to ask for help and delegate where I can. I’m trying to focus on tasks that only I can do. I’m also learning to keep emails more brief and not send essays/rants that require a long time to compose (if I need to, I set up a meeting or a quick phone call). I’ve also avoided browsing on social media as I tend to get sucked in easily and need to save my precious screen time for work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I downloaded an app called &lt;a href=&quot;http://iamfutureproof.com/tools/awareness/&quot;&gt;awareness&lt;/a&gt; (mac) that gives you a soft reminder (the sound of a meditation bowl ringing) whenever your designated work duration is up, and automatically resets itself when you’ve taken a break for your designated break duration. It also shows how long you’ve been using your computer without a break in the task bar. I found this helps keep me from idly using my computer and reminds me to give my eyes and brain a short screen break (&amp;gt; 3 minutes) every 20 minutes or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also been sporting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00BQ7KBV4/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o04_s00?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&quot;&gt;computer glasses&lt;/a&gt; when I look at any sort of screen for more than a few seconds, which help reduce eye strain and definitely seem to help prevent my headaches. I didn’t have an appreciation for how aggressive projector screens and fluorescent lights are until my head injury, and these really help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to charge my laptop up for the day, and then use it on battery power throughout the day. I try to plan out any writing or work I have to do on a piece of paper before I start so I’m focused on the task at hand when I open my laptop up. If I run through the battery in a day, it’s a sign that I should consider taking the rest of the day easy to give myself a rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anyone has other thoughts on more efficient/mindful computer use, I’d love to hear more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="concussion" /><category term="quantified self" /><summary type="html">I’ve been recovering from Post-Concussion Syndrome for the past 7 weeks or so. Now that I’ve been getting back to work, I wanted to share a few things that I’ve found particularly helpful for keeping up with my work without hurting my brain.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Email Vacation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/23/my-email-vacation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Email Vacation" /><published>2014-07-23T01:37:21-04:00</published><updated>2014-07-23T01:37:21-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/07/23/my-email-vacation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/23/my-email-vacation.html">&lt;p&gt;I spent the last 10 days or so on vacation. Before I left, I wrote &lt;a href=&quot;http://maggiedelano.tumblr.com/2020/07/11/2014-07-10-a-real-vacation.html&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; post about trying to make my vacation as relaxing as possible, which for me involved banning myself from all but the most important e-mails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To recap briefly, I told everyone who might need something from me before vacation that I’d be gone, and did my best to tie up loose ends before hand. Then, I made all email skip my inbox, except emails that were sent directly to maggie.delano+vacation@gmail.com. I updated my autoresponder to inform people that I would not receive their email until my return unless they sent it to the above address. I deleted the gmail app from my phone, left my laptop at home, and went on vacation. Here’s how it went:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email checking frequency:&lt;/strong&gt; I found it incredibly tempting to check my email for the first 12 hours or so, but once I got to Portland, I only checked my email once or twice a day for relevant logistics emails from friends. When I arrived in SF, I had to reply to one work related email, but then everything else was logistics emails from friends. I found myself checking my email a bit more frequently when I knew a thread was actively going on, but nudged myself to stop checking so regularly once I picked up on the fact that I was doing this. In Vegas, I didn’t check email too much, and when I realized that there were no more logistics to coordinate (and hence no more relevant emails to look out for), I stopped all together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emails received: &lt;/strong&gt; Everyone who needed to get in touch with me complied with my +vacation request. There wasn’t a single email that I received when I got back that I needed to have responded to earlier, and only one important work thread that required the +vacation label at all. All other +vacation emails were trip logistics or from people I had “whitelisted.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phone usage&lt;/strong&gt; : I found that once I had freed myself from my email, I used my phone a lot less. I realized that checking email/twitter are like tics for me, and are something I do immediately if I get a bit bored or stressed. Disconnecting made me feel a lot more present. I expected that I might just spend a lot of time on twitter or facebook, but I actually didn’t go on twitter until half way through my trip, when I started to have more downtime and wanted to have things to talk about with people who weren’t living in my vacation bubble. I checked facebook once during the week to approve friend requests, and then checked it a bunch in Vegas because people were posting photos of me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cheating&lt;/strong&gt; : All emails were labelled “ruinyourvacation.” I didn’t check that label until I got home, which I’m pretty happy about. I did, however, check my sent messages twice to make sure my emails were sent over the gmail web interface, and saw the contents of a few of my “sent” autoresponder messages. These didn’t really give me a sense of the email contents, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coming back&lt;/strong&gt; : I had about 500 email threads to sort through after I got back. I deleted all mailing list spam first (and unsubscribed from things while I was at it). This brought me down to about 300 threads. Then I went through the emails that were left, archived the ones I didn’t need to reply to, and created filters for those types of emails to skip my inbox in the future. Finally, I went through and replied to emails that I needed to. This only added up to about 15 emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall&lt;/strong&gt; : My vacation was incredibly relaxing, and I’m really glad I made the decision to spare myself the contents of my inbox. Having a break from keeping track of so many things at once was really, really nice. It felt amazing to go about my day relatively worry-free. I joked that the only downside of my “urgent only” email policy was that it didn’t also apply to my text messages. There were a few times when people texted me about things that weren’t urgent and stressed me out a bit, which is one potential downside of taking a vacation “on the grid,” rather than off it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving forward: &lt;/strong&gt; I’m definitely going to implement an email vacation again. I’m also considering implementing mini-vacations over the weekends. I’ve been thinking about the mobile vs. PC use cases for checking email, and am experimenting with enabling push notifications for “important” emails on my phone so that I’m notified when an email I’m waiting for comes in, rather than refreshing my inbox constantly. I’d also like a more permanent solution like my +vacation filter so that I can toggle on which types of email I receive over weekends or breaks (my work and personal email separation is pretty poor as I used my @mit.edu address as my main address for many years before getting a gmail.com address). Will report back on how that all goes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="email" /><category term="vacation" /><category term="emailvacation" /><category term="habits" /><category term="quantified self" /><summary type="html">I spent the last 10 days or so on vacation. Before I left, I wrote this post about trying to make my vacation as relaxing as possible, which for me involved banning myself from all but the most important e-mails.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Real Vacation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/10/a-real-vacation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Real Vacation" /><published>2014-07-10T22:53:00-04:00</published><updated>2014-07-10T22:53:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/07/10/a-real-vacation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/10/a-real-vacation.html">&lt;p&gt;Grad school has been particularly stressful and hectic the past few months, so I’m super excited to be taking a 10 day vacation starting tomorrow. I’ll be flying to Portland, then to SF, then to Las Vegas, and then back home to Boston!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I’ve been planning for my vacation, I’ve been thinking about what it means to take a “real” vacation. What do I need to do for myself to properly de-stress?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I’ve noticed about myself is that checking email on vacation almost always winds up stressing me out. One frustrating email request or grade report, and I can get bent out of shape for the rest of the day when I’m supposed to be relaxing and enjoying myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want this vacation to be different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to allow myself to truly decompress, I’ve decided to pledge to check my email as infrequently as possible. And when I do check it, I’ll only check it for specific things like coordinating logistics with friends. I’m also leaving my laptop at home so I don’t get tempted to do any work or check my email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I’ve gotten closer to actually taking the vacation, I’ve been feeling nervous about &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; committing to not checking my email. So I’ve been planning out how to make this pledge a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by danah boyd’s article on &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.mit.edu/maggied/www/resume_mkd.pdf&quot;&gt;How To Take An Email Sabbatical&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/5836537/the-most-cleverest-vacation-auto-reply-e-mail-ive-seen&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; clever autoresponder message, here’s what I’ve done:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action Items and Collaborators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Made a clear list of everything I’m working on and identified concrete milestones to complete before vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Completed those milestones as best as I could and sent a status update to anyone else involved.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Told anyone I’m working on something with that I would be away on vacation starting a few weeks ago and that if they need anything from me, they should ask me before I leave.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roughly planned out what I want to do the week I get back and set a few reminders for myself, so I don’t feel totally swamped and stressed right after vacation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travel Logistics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Told anyone I think might need to contact me (such as people I’m meeting up with while traveling), that they should include maggie.delano+vacation@gmail.com on an email thread, and I’ll respond to their messages.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signed up for auto check-in for my flights and downloaded the United app to my phone so I have all my travel information accessible. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Made a note in Evernote with all relevant addresses and confirmation numbers, so I don’t need to look them up in email and be tempted to break the pledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Gmail:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Created a filter than applies the label “ruinyourvacation” to all incoming email and skips the inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Created a filter that applies the label “vacation” to any email sent to maggie.delano+vacation@gmail.com.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whitelisted a few specific email addresses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enabled my autoresponder with a message that explains I’m on vacation, and to re-send the email to me only if it’s urgent, or there’s a good reason I need to see it (e.g. group logistics threads).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pre-applied the “vacation” label to existing logistics threads, in case I need to refer to them or forgot to put something on my Evernote note.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deleted the Gmail application from my phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite all this effort, I’ve still checked my email at least three times while writing this post. I think this will be a real challenge, but I’m interested to see where it goes. I’ll report back when I get home.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="email" /><category term="vacation" /><category term="emailvacation" /><category term="habits" /><summary type="html">Grad school has been particularly stressful and hectic the past few months, so I’m super excited to be taking a 10 day vacation starting tomorrow. I’ll be flying to Portland, then to SF, then to Las Vegas, and then back home to Boston!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Code of Conduct</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/06/a-code-of-conduct.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Code of Conduct" /><published>2014-07-06T16:14:53-04:00</published><updated>2014-07-06T16:14:53-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/07/06/a-code-of-conduct</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/07/06/a-code-of-conduct.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantifiedself.com/2014/06/code-conduct/&quot;&gt;A Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrote this blog post for the Quantified Self blog. I’m excited to see where these improvements take us as a community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="quantified self" /><category term="code of conduct" /><summary type="html">A Code of Conduct</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vegan Eats</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/06/22/vegan-eats.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vegan Eats" /><published>2014-06-22T20:42:35-04:00</published><updated>2014-06-22T20:42:35-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/06/22/vegan-eats</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/06/22/vegan-eats.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been eating &lt;a href=&quot;http://maggiedelano.tumblr.com/2020/07/11/2014-05-05-reflections-after-a-month-of-veganism-during-the.html-week&quot;&gt;vegan during the week&lt;/a&gt; for almost three months now. I thought it would be pretty challenging to eat vegan and also purchase most of my meals (I’ve been busy, and haven’t had much time for cooking). Fortunately, though, I’ve found a few different vegan options at restaurants in Cambridge and Somerville that I really like. Here are some of my current favorites:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bloc11.com/menu/sandwiches/&quot;&gt;The Atticus&lt;/a&gt; at Bloc 11 Cafe&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;- &lt;/strong&gt; buffalo tempeh with avocado spread, tomato, red onion, and greens on rye. I tried this for the first time two weeks ago, and love it. Ask for it toasted.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cloverfoodlab.com/food/&quot;&gt;Chickpea Fritter&lt;/a&gt; at Clover&lt;/strong&gt; - hummus, israeli salad, pickles, falafel, pickled vegetables and tahini. Crunchy and amazing. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chana Masala and Toor Dal at &lt;a href=&quot;http://dining.mit.edu/venues-menus/cafespice&quot;&gt;Cafe Spice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - chickpeas, yellow lentils, and rice. Simple but probably one of my favorite lunch time options.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most chain restaurants also have a vegan option, or you can order a vegetarian option without cheese. The sofritas from Chipotle is delicious, as is the hummus and veggie sandwich from Cosi.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="vegan" /><category term="veganism" /><summary type="html">I’ve been eating vegan during the week for almost three months now. I thought it would be pretty challenging to eat vegan and also purchase most of my meals (I’ve been busy, and haven’t had much time for cooking). Fortunately, though, I’ve found a few different vegan options at restaurants in Cambridge and Somerville that I really like. Here are some of my current favorites:</summary></entry></feed>